JACK WITBROCK FINLAY

ADDRESS: 3/12 Clare Place, Mt Wellington, Auckland, New Zealand

PHONE: +64 22 603 5912 EMAIL: jack@jackfinlay.com

WEB: jackfinlay.com

GITHUB: github.com/JackWFinlay

Summary

 Building a successful career in software development. Skilled in full-stack .NET and database development. Constantly seeking to further skills and education through independent study.

Technical Skills

Skill	Experience
C#, ASP.NET, .NET Framework & .NET Core	3 years
JavaScript, JQuery	3 years
SQL	4 years
Version Control (Git, GitHub, Bitbucket)	4 years
Databases (Microsoft SQL Server, Oracle)	3 Years
Agile Methodologies (SCRUM, Kanban)	4 Years
Agile Tools (Jira, Confluence, TFS, VSTS)	3 Years

Education

Auckland University of Technology, Auckland, New Zealand 2013 - 2016

 Bachelor of Computer and Information Science - Software Development Major.

Topics covered included: Software Development in C# and Java, Object-Oriented Design and Development, Databases, Agile Methodologies, Information security, Data process Modelling, Project Management, Discrete Mathematics and Linear Algebra, Data Structures, and Algorithms.

Experience

Software Developer AlphaCert Labs Itd, Auckland

March 2018 - Present

- C#, HTML/CSS/JavaScript, ASP.NET MVC with Entity Framework
- Microsoft SQL Server T-SQL development

Full-stack ASP.Net MVC developer role. Developing in C#, HTML/CSS, and JavaScript. ETL and data transformation in C# with MEF. T-SQL database development, database migrations via Fluent Migrator.

Analyst Programmer Gentrack Itd, Auckland

August 2016 - March 2018

- BASIC Variant
- Analysis, Debugging
- Microsoft SQL Server, Oracle Database development

Defect fixes and extension of functionality of utilities billing software. Data analysis and database development using SQL. Collaboration with internal and external clients to achieve consistent results.

Technical Consultant Business Mechanix Itd, Auckland

April 2015 - August 2016

- C#, HTML/CSS/JavaScript, ASP.NET MVC with Entity Framework
- SPARQL RDF API
- Microsoft SQL Server development

Developed a website for international students to find study options in New Zealand. Managed and mentored a team of three interns working over the 2015/16 summer. Setup and managed Azure virtual machines, maintenance of C# applications, and ad-hoc customer support.

Intern Developer December 2014 - February 2015 University of Auckland IT Services, Auckland

Java, Scriptella, Bash

Intern developer role at IT Services. Existing and new projects. Developed an HTTP driver for Scriptella from the source code. Various ad-hoc Scriptella, Groovy and Bash scripts.

References

References available on request